husdal.com 2014-05-27

# Privacy Policy • Supply Chain Risk | Business Continuity | Transport Vulnerability

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by husdal.com and how it is used.

### Cookies

husdal.com uses several services that may set **cookie** s in your browsers, most importantly:

  * GetClicky
  * Google Analytics
  * Quantcast
  * Incapsula
  * Google AdSense

The cookies we want to set are for analytics and security purposes only. These tell us things such as how visitors get to our site, what pages on our site were looked at, and how long people stay for. It tells us what countries people are browsing from, but it does not tell us who those people are.

husdal.com has no access to or control over these **cookies that are used by these third-parties**. You should consult **the respective privacy policies** of these third-parties (See links below) for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. **www.husdal.com’s privacy policy does not apply to** , and we cannot control the activities of the third parties mentioned below:

[ **GetClicky**](http://www.getclicky.com/) is used for collecting website usage statistics. The information that is collected includes, but not limited to, internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/entry/visited/exit pages,  to analyze trends, administer the site, and track user’s movement around the site.  IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. GetClicky sets the “_jsuid” cookie, which allows GetClicky to creating [the following usage profile](http://getclicky.com/stats/?site_id=119721). More information can be found in the [GetClicky Privacy](http://getclicky.com/#/terms) terms.

[ **Google Analytics**](http://www.google.com/analytics/) is used for website statistics in a similar manner as GetClicky. Google Analytics sets “_utma”, “_utmb”, “_utmc” and “_utmz” cookies. More information can be found in [cookies and Google Analytics](http://code.google.com/apis/analytics/docs/concepts/gaConceptsCookies.html).

[ **Quantcast**](http://www.quantcast.com/) is used for website statistics and demographic information. It sets the “_qcb” cookie. This allows Quantcast to create [the following profile](http://www.quantcast.com/husdal.com). More information can be found in the [Quantcast Privacy Policy](http://www.quantcast.com/privacy) terms.

 **[Incapsula](http://www.incapsula.com/)** is is used for website security and adds a cookie in order to maintain a user session. Incapsula intelligently builds the reputation of users across its network through the use of cookies and other mechanisms in order to try and achieve the goal of allowing all legitimate users on to sites, but blocking all attackers and threats. Incapsula sets a “incap_” cookie. More information can be found under [How it works](http://www.incapsula.com/how-it-works/website-security) on the Incapsula website.

[ **Google AdSense**](http://www.google.com/adsense/), as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on husdal.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to husdal.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Some of our **other advertising partners** may use cookies, e.g.:

  * Amazon
  * Wiley

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on husdal.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

If you wish to **disable cookies** , you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### E-mail

husdal.com will not retain any details that you provide, except for **your e-mail address** when you leave a comment on this site. The e-mail will never be disclosed to third parties, nor will it be used for unsolicited emails to you.

### Links

This website contains **links to other websites**. Please be aware that husdal.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you, when you leave this website, to read the privacy statements/policies of each and every website you visit, as this particular privacy policy applies solely to this particular website.
